[{"id": "liar_0", "prompt": "Two weeks ago, a man entered the worlds busiest airport in Atlanta, Georgia, carrying a loaded AR-15 automatic weapon with an extended-capacity, 100-round magazine.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_1", "prompt": "By declaring that Pluto was no longer a planet, the (International Astronomical Union) put into place a planetary definition that would have even declassified Earth as a planet if it existed as far from the sun as Pluto does.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_2", "prompt": "Two-thirds of the federal budget is permanent law ... its permanently appropriated.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_3", "prompt": "Wars in Afghanistan and Iraq have cost every U.S. family $45,000.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_4", "prompt": "In New York City, murders are up.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_5", "prompt": "Obama \"remains silent\" and \"is never asked how he feels about his church honoring Farrakhan.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_6", "prompt": "Says a rather extraordinary amount of non-classroom employees were added by Texas school districts over the last decade.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_7", "prompt": "Says President Barack Obama made unilateral changes to Obamacare 38 times.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_8", "prompt": "\"Ronald Reagan faced an even worse recession\" than the current one.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_9", "prompt": "Weve cut the deficit by two-thirds.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_10", "prompt": "A North Carolina study proves that probably over a million people voted twice in (the 2012) election.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_11", "prompt": "In Rhode Island today, 25 percent of our households either dont have a bank account at all, or they have a bank account and theyre still relying on high-cost financial services like payday loans, pawn shop check cashing and so on.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_12", "prompt": "Says drug dealers have overdosed on purpose to avoid prosecution.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_13", "prompt": "Says he is the only candidate in the race for Clackamas County Chair who will refuse to join the Public Employees Retirement System.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_14", "prompt": "\"Charlie Crist was the only prominent Republican in the country to campaign with Barack Obama before the stimulus passed, on behalf of the stimulus.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_15", "prompt": "Only one out of 10 minimum wage workers today are teen age or a young person.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_16", "prompt": "Prior to Obamacare here in Wisconsin, 95 percent of Wisconsinites were covered by insurance. After Obamacare, 95 percent of Wisconsinites were covered by insurance. It hasnt had an impact.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_17", "prompt": "Gun marketplaces on Facebook mean ANYONE can broker a deal on a gun online, meet the seller in a parking lot somewhere, and walk away with a weapon.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_18", "prompt": "We now do have evidence that Donald Trump is being used as a recruiting tool for terrorists.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_19", "prompt": "When mentioning Villanovas buzzer-beating win in the national championships, Hillary Clinton said: I love those come-from-behind victories.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_20", "prompt": "Homicides last year increased by 17 percent in Americas 50 largest cities. Thats the largest increase in 25 years.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_21", "prompt": "When (Joe Kyrillos) had an opportunity to vote for women in terms of their health care, not once, not twice, but six times, he voted against womens health care in our state.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_22", "prompt": "During the Bush administration, you actually had a prominent liberal write a book about how Bush was preparing for a fascist takeover of this country.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_23", "prompt": "Patrick Murphy voted for Obamacare in 2010, yet he reversed himself and voted to delay the employer mandate and the individual mandate.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_24", "prompt": "Federal stimulus money went to a Georgia Tech project that will apparently involve the professor jamming with world-renowned musicians to hopefully also create satisfying works of art.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_25", "prompt": "A school uniform policy helps with school safety, helps with truancy.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_26", "prompt": "The IRS filed an $11,000 lien against (Allen) West for back taxes. Three liens were placed on his home for unpaid bills, and a judge ordered West to pay over $5,000 for past due credit card bills.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_27", "prompt": "To vote in Mexico every eligible Mexican citizen has to have a tamper-proof photo-ID card with a thumbprint and an embossed hologram.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_28", "prompt": "Today there are more men and women out of work in America than there are people working in Canada.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_29", "prompt": "Says the U.S. fleet of attack submarines is scheduled to fall below the 48 boats that Navy says it needs to carry out current missions.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_30", "prompt": "Says new estimates from the Congressional Budget Office conclude the final price-tag for the health care law will exceed $2 trillion more than double what was initially reported.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_31", "prompt": "Says Mitt Romney called the Arizona law a model for the nation.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_32", "prompt": "The Wisconsin Retirement System for public employees is a self-funded pension plan and its the money of the workers that funds it.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_33", "prompt": "Americans spend more than $160 billion and 6 billion hours per year complying with the tax code.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_34", "prompt": "When John Kasich became governor of Ohio, there was an $8 billion budget deficit and now theres a $2 billion surplus.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_35", "prompt": "As state treasurer, Alexi Giannoulias lost $73 million in our kids college savings.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_36", "prompt": "Four times, I said, he (John McCain)is a hero, but you know ... people choose selective pieces.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_37", "prompt": "\"I have never voted for a tax increase.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_38", "prompt": "If Congress does not pass the renewal of the payroll tax cut before the end of the year, nearly 160 million working families will see their taxes go up by roughly $1,000.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_39", "prompt": "\"When you look at the nearly 150 men and women who have served us on the Texas Supreme Court, more than half of them had zero prior judicial experience.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_40", "prompt": "There are many studies that indicate that the longer people get unemployment insurance, it provides some disincentive to work.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_41", "prompt": "The United States is the only advanced country on Earth that doesnt guarantee paid maternity leave to our workers.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_42", "prompt": "\"Usually it's about $900 a month to get health coverage. (Florida's program has) reduced that, on average, to about $150 a month.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_43", "prompt": "The 2011-13 state budget cuts overall funding for public schools by $1.6 billion", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_44", "prompt": "On U.S.-Israeli relations, Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu set the record straight he said, our two countries have exactly the same policy (and) our security cooperation is unprecedented.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_45", "prompt": "\"Privatizing Social Security was a bad idea when George W. Bush proposed it. It's a bad idea today. Sen. McCain's campaign went even further ... suggesting ... to cut cost-of-living adjustments or to raise the retirement age.\"", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_46", "prompt": "Says Mitch McConnell voted to raise Medicare costs for a current Kentucky senior by $6,000.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_47", "prompt": "Democratic Party candidates for the state Assembly actually received 200,000 more votes statewide than their Republican counterparts in the 2012 election", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_48", "prompt": "Says the governor is going around the state talking about [how] we should fund an income tax cut that benefits higher income earners and not lower income earners", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_49", "prompt": "The impact of the 2010 federal health care legislation will be huge on Georgia.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_50", "prompt": "\"You ... said that Barack Obama was not ready to be commander in chief.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_51", "prompt": "Texas women make an average of $8,355 less per year than men doing the very same job.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_52", "prompt": "Says library district would come at no direct cost to the city budget.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_53", "prompt": "If youre a Mexican, you get sent back. ... But if youre from a noncontiguous country like the Central American countries then you can stay in the United States.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_54", "prompt": "In 2009, Democratic Wisconsin state senators rammed through a billion-dollar tax hike in 24 hours with no public input.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_55", "prompt": "Abortions account for 94 percent of the services provided for pregnant women by Planned Parenthood.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_56", "prompt": "George Allen had 40,000 earmarks while he was a senator.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_57", "prompt": "Says Marco Rubio would take away a womans right to choose for victims of rape or incest.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_58", "prompt": "Says Georgia Power customers pay 10 percent to 15 percent below the national average for electricity.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_59", "prompt": "Some city of Atlanta employees have not had raises in eight years.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_60", "prompt": "Says Russ Feingold said that with Obamacare, we could keep our doctors and our plans, it was rated as the Lie of the Year.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_61", "prompt": "Says that he did not exactly say that communities have the right to ban mosques.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_62", "prompt": "We jumped 11 places since beginning this year in terms of being job-friendly.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_63", "prompt": "Says Hillary Clinton has taken hundreds of millions from those countries where women are stoned, where women are killed for adulteryand women cant drive.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_64", "prompt": "Scott Walker to cut $300 million from universities, spend $500 million on a pro basketball stadium.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_65", "prompt": "On HealthCare.Gov, Texan Mark Sullivan found a good health insurance plan that includes dental, for less than $80 a month.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_66", "prompt": "Since last years address, more than 10,000 jobs created -- many on the high end of the employment scale.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_67", "prompt": "\"Our economy could fall $1 trillion short of its full capacity, which translates into more than $12,000 in lost income for a family of four.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_68", "prompt": "Suzanne Bonamici was the only no vote on a 2009 bill cracking down on drunk drivers.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_69", "prompt": "\"The Democratic Congress has already taken significant steps to create jobs and jump-start the economy, resulting in the lowest tax rates in over 50 years and the creation of over 500,000 new jobs so far this year.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_70", "prompt": "He received \"A\" ratings from \"every conservative organization that gives ratings.\"", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_71", "prompt": "Poverty levels (are) at an all-time high.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_72", "prompt": "Planned Parenthood has now (been) found to also illegally sell baby parts.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_73", "prompt": "Any child born prematurely, according to the president, in his own words, can be killed.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_74", "prompt": "Right now in Georgia, nearly one in three leaving our prisons are re-convicted within three years.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_75", "prompt": "Says your Legislative Assembly was within one vote of enacting each of those bills into Oregon law.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_76", "prompt": "Says Republicans supported legislation on early voting and in-person voting in 2005.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_77", "prompt": "The Paul Ryan budget proposal would privatize Medicare.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_78", "prompt": "Says Barack Obama has added $16 trillion to the national debt.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_79", "prompt": "Women are still paid 82 cents for every dollar a man earns in Texas.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_80", "prompt": "15 years ago, cancer drugs cost an average of $10,000 a year. Now its $10,000 a month.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_81", "prompt": "A referendum gives the people the chance to decide on cutting the Milwaukee County Board budget by two-thirds", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_82", "prompt": "Paul Ryan is one of less than a dozen Republican congressmen to have voted for every bailout to come before Congress.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_83", "prompt": "The national debt is on track to double during Obamas presidency.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_84", "prompt": "Its coming. Nobody can stop this train.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_85", "prompt": "It has been estimated that nearly 40 percent of all guns sold in America are sold by private, unlicensed sellers either online or through gun shows.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_86", "prompt": "Says Gov. Rick Perry has been begging for the federal government to send the Coast Guard to patrol two lakes on the U.S.-Mexico border.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_87", "prompt": "Says Donald Trump is going to go out and carpet bomb the Middle East.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_88", "prompt": "As many as a quarter of our students arent even finishing high school.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_89", "prompt": "Preventive care saves money, for families, for businesses, for government, for everybody.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_90", "prompt": "In 67 different ways, Governor McCrory has raised taxes on middle income families.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_91", "prompt": "Says John Raese said he wants 1,000 laser systems put in the sky, and we need it right now.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_92", "prompt": "The 9-0 decision last week was the 13th time the Supreme Court voted 9-0 that the president had exceeded his constitutional authority.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_93", "prompt": "Says that in his book, Rick Perry said that Social Security is unconstitutional.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_94", "prompt": "Social Security has nothing to do with the federal deficit.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_95", "prompt": "When Moammar Gadhafi was set to visit the United Nations, and no one would let him stay in New York, Trump allowed Gadhafi to set up an elaborate tent at his Westchester County (New York) estate.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_96", "prompt": "When was the last time you saw a Chevrolet in Japan? It doesnt exist, folks.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_97", "prompt": "Says Mitt Romney flip-flopped on an assault weapons ban.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_98", "prompt": "The children coming across the southern U.S. border were never examined after they got here and quarantined if they had a disease. They were just sent out across the country. Many of them had measles ... We now have an outbreak of it all because of our immigration policy.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_99", "prompt": "This is the first time in Texas history -- and only the fourth time in United States history -- that two women are running for the top spots.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_100", "prompt": "Nearly 90% of Travis County government races will be settled by the time of the Democratic primary.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_101", "prompt": "Says 11 straight years of no major hurricanes striking land in the United States bores a hole right through the whole climate change argument.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_102", "prompt": "In Miami-Dade County, we spend at our school system over $20 million every year educating recent immigrants.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_103", "prompt": "The Koch network (is) spending more money (in a Senate race) in Ohio than anywhere else in the country.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_104", "prompt": "Due to over-incarceration in 1950, two out of three young black men were in the workforce. Today, its one out of three black men are in the workforce.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_105", "prompt": "Says hes proposed the largest employer contribution to the Virginia Retirement System in history.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_106", "prompt": "Birth control pioneer Margaret Sanger wasan active participant in the Ku Klux Klan.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_107", "prompt": "Says Jill McCabe supports late term abortions. Larger baby parts are more profitable.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_108", "prompt": "Alex Sink was \"the first official who said that BP should pay $25 million for an ad campaign to promote Florida tourism.\"", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_109", "prompt": "Says Mitt Romneys comments indicated he would not have pursued Osama bin Laden.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_110", "prompt": "Since 1968, more Americans have died from gunfire than died in all the wars of this countrys history.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_111", "prompt": "The state covered a smaller percentage of the cost of K-12 education in 2013 than it did in 2002.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_112", "prompt": "While fighting a move to toughen penalties for workplace gender discrimination, state Sen. Glenn Grothman said he didnt believe women belonged in the workplace but belonged at home, cooking and cleaning and having babies.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_113", "prompt": "Republicans enacted the most drastic cuts to K-12 public schools of any state in the nation.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_114", "prompt": "Rick Scott got a majority of the Hispanic vote in Florida.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_115", "prompt": "The University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee has 2.8 students per faculty member, tied for second-lowest in its history since 1994.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_116", "prompt": "While in the Illinois Senate, Barack Obama passed legislation moving people \"from welfare to jobs.\"", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_117", "prompt": "Cervical cancer in Africa is fully preventable with basic education, screeningand vaccines.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_118", "prompt": "In Texas, sexting is a felony sex offense for teenagers that can mean up to 10 years in prison.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_119", "prompt": "Says Glenn Grothman pushed through state tax credits that when phased in, someone that owns a factory that produces millions in income will pay less tax than their nephew would if he worked full time at Taco Bell for minimum wage.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_120", "prompt": "Says U.S. Senate rival Tammy Baldwin wants a completely government-controlled health care system that goes far beyond Obamacare and is a Medicare system for all.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_121", "prompt": "Theres no plan from Senate Democrats or the White House to replace the sequester.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_122", "prompt": "Says U.S. Senate opponent Ron Johnson is opposed to all government-assisted student loans.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_123", "prompt": "Health care reform: Everything about it is going to raise costs, raise taxes and lower the quality of health care.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_124", "prompt": "SaysGary Johnson and the Libertarian Party want to get rid of the public school system.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_125", "prompt": "\"Bill Richardson passed the first law in the nation giving National Guard soldiers $400,000 in life insurance.\"", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_126", "prompt": "Says 80 percent of the health care dollars are spent by 20 percent of the population.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_127", "prompt": "Says Ted Cruz has pledged to eliminate the U.S. Department of Education, which would end federal aid to college students.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_128", "prompt": "You look at defense were spending more than the rest of the world combined.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_129", "prompt": "Says under the new health care law the patient-doctor relationship will be eliminated.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_130", "prompt": "Under Lee Fisher Ohio has lost nearly 400,000 jobs.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_131", "prompt": "Texas has 600,000 registered voters who dont have the kind of photo ID needed to vote.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_132", "prompt": "Says U.S. Rep. Debbie Wasserman Schultz voted to cut off Floridas veterans and their benefits.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_133", "prompt": "SaysJeb Bush significantly cut early voting prior to the 2008 presidential election.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_134", "prompt": "As a Member of Congress, Chris Murphy was raking in $1 million in salary.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_135", "prompt": "Says New Jersey lost private-sector jobs between 2000 and 2009 because Democrats increased taxes, fees, regulations and state spending.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_136", "prompt": "Under the new Arizona immigration law, police can't stop someone to check their immigration status unless they think they see something illegal.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_137", "prompt": "Says Lois Frankel took a 40 percent pay raise as mayor while West Palm Beach lost jobs.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_138", "prompt": "Rick Perry had planned to retire from the legislature until his best friend, David Weeks, and I talked him into switching parties and running for the GOP nomination for agriculture commissioner.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_139", "prompt": "Says she was the first in her family to go to a four-year college.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_140", "prompt": "Says Republican U.S. Senate candidate Ted Cruz opposes the DREAM Act, which is supported by 85% of Latinos.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_141", "prompt": "Says India gained jobs thanks to Romney.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_142", "prompt": "Ive got a 94 percent career voting record in Congress while Bill Nelson has a 92 percent voting record.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_143", "prompt": "Today, when people retire in Galveston County, Texas, they retire making at least 50 percent more than they would ever get out of Social Security.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_144", "prompt": "A violent felon can buy (a gun) over the Internet with no background check, no questions asked.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_145", "prompt": "Says Barack Obama put in place a board that can tell people ultimately what treatments theyre going to receive.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_146", "prompt": "Christmas trees are grown in all 50 States.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_147", "prompt": "\"Dubai is the only country with huge amounts of imported workers that's actually passed legislation to give these immigrant workers a better deal in the Middle East.\"", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_148", "prompt": "98 percent of American families make under $250,000 a year.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_149", "prompt": "Seventy percent of the people in the state of New Jersey want marriage equality.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_150", "prompt": "My state of Florida is now the third-largest state. We have surpassed New York in population.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_151", "prompt": "You wonder why you dont see Rand Paul as much; hes still shopping for his billionaire. Hes like the only one who hasnt found a billionaire to fund his super PAC.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_152", "prompt": "President Barack Obama has now spent three years proving that he kills jobs in energy, he kills jobs in manufacturing.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_153", "prompt": "Rob Portmans plan to tax, slash and privatize Social Security would devastate Ohioans.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_154", "prompt": "Youve got each day 10,000 new seniors, baby boomers, becoming eligible for the entitlement programs.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_155", "prompt": "Alex Sink wants to cut Medicare.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_156", "prompt": "In the last 6 years, there have been 420 elections for State Senator and State Representative. Only three incumbents have been defeated!", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_157", "prompt": "We created as many jobs in the first six months of this year as we did in all of 2011 and 2011 was the best single year for private-sector job growth since the year 2000.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_158", "prompt": "Jorge Elorza wants to impose a municipal income tax.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_159", "prompt": "By 12th grade, more than 3 out of 10 girls have been pregnant at least once.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_160", "prompt": "Ninety six percent of employers in the Granite State are considered small businesses.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_161", "prompt": "The CDC is spending money on things like jazzercise, urban gardening and massage therapy that could be redirected to Ebola.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_162", "prompt": "My campaign finished the last quarter reporting the most cash on hand of any Republican in the field $13.8 million in the bank, $3.5 million more than the Jeb Bush campaign.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_163", "prompt": "Twenty-four percent of doctors in Virginia currently dont accept new Medicaid patients because the reimbursement rates are so low.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_164", "prompt": "A recent report from the presidents deficit commission was completely empty on controlling health care costs.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_165", "prompt": "We did not even have a federal income tax in this country until 1913.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_166", "prompt": "Since I took office, over 319,000 new private sector jobs have been created in Georgia with nearly 93,000 of those coming in the past 12 months.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_167", "prompt": "The Super Bowl has one of the highest levels of human sex trafficking activity of any event in the country.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_168", "prompt": "Says $38 billion in spending cuts in federal budget compromise is less than $1 billion in real cuts.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_169", "prompt": "Says Mitt Romney said he does not line up with the NRA.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_170", "prompt": "Marco Rubio has the No. 1absentee record in the United States Senate.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_171", "prompt": "Says Rick Scott has teamed up with a felon convicted of running a Ponzi scheme to smear Charlie Crist.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_172", "prompt": "The U.S. would gainrevenue by cutting personal income tax rates in half and ending tax breaks.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_173", "prompt": "As Jim Doyles Commerce secretary, Mary Burke spent $12.5 million dollars to buy a vacant lot for a company that said it had no plans to create jobs in Wisconsin and had laid off 800 workers.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_174", "prompt": "At this particular point in time, looking at the field, theres only one individual thats ever had the uniform of his country onand thats me.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_175", "prompt": "There have been literally hundreds of new tax preferences and loopholes added to the code since 1986, last time we did this.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_176", "prompt": "\"With one stroke of his pen, President Bush has denied health insurance to 3.8 million kids who were due to get it under this bipartisan expansion of the Children's Health Insurance Program.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_177", "prompt": "Medicare passed with virtually no Republican support.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_178", "prompt": "Protesters caused $7.5 million in damage to the Wisconsin State House", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_179", "prompt": "Do you know that we have pipes carrying natural gas in this country that are made of wood? Im not joking.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_180", "prompt": "If you care about the environment, weve got record funding.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_181", "prompt": "Im the only candidate in the Democratic primary, or actually on either side, who Wall Street financiers and hedge fund managers are actually running ads against.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_182", "prompt": "The Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Court is transparent.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_183", "prompt": "The Milwaukee business community did not speak about the facts -- and in support of train manufacturer Talgo -- as the Milwaukee-Madison rail link was being killed.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_184", "prompt": "Says Marco Rubio knows full well I voted for his amendment to increase military spending to $697 billion.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_185", "prompt": "Sheldon Whitehouse voted for a $525-billion tax increase on the middle class.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_186", "prompt": "Under Randi Shade, Austin has had the highest cost of living of any large Texas city.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_187", "prompt": "In 2006, Charlie Crist opposed in-state tuition for illegal immigrants.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_188", "prompt": "The median net worth of American households hasnt changed much over the past decades, its about $20,000 ... but Congress average median net worth has ballooned, more than doubled.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_189", "prompt": "The Obama administrations green stimulus program funneled close to $2 billion dollars to overseas firms, creating thousands of jobs in China.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_190", "prompt": "Florida has the second-lowest (campaign) contribution limit in the entire country.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_191", "prompt": "It is senior citizens, not Hispanics, who are the fastest-growing demographic in this country.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_192", "prompt": "On whether the federal debt limit should be raised", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_193", "prompt": "On whether hes had a relationship with Vladimir Putin.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_194", "prompt": "Says of 80,000 people who were denied a firearm in 2012 due to a failed background check, only 44 were prosecuted.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_195", "prompt": "There havent been tax cuts for the rich in Rhode Island.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_196", "prompt": "Chris Christie has not increased the taxes on anyone.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_197", "prompt": "The State of Texas is funding womens health services at historically high levels; they just increased their level another $50 million for the next two years.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_198", "prompt": "Roy Cooper wont say how he will pay for free college tuition.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_199", "prompt": "\"There are no earmarks\" in the stimulus bill.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_200", "prompt": "Says Scott Brown voted with President Barack Obama 70 percent of the time in 2011.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_201", "prompt": "Says House Republicans tried to change the definition of rape.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_202", "prompt": "The Republican Party has 21 percent party ID and shrinking.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_203", "prompt": "\"I do provide universal health care.\"", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_204", "prompt": "Says his administration balanced two budgets with over $13 billion in deficits without raising taxes.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_205", "prompt": "Says the California flag was supposed to be apear, not a bear.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_206", "prompt": "Because of the health care act, The people who have health care and like it in this county are not going to be able to keep what they have.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_207", "prompt": "More Americans have lost their jobs under Barack Obama than any president in modern history.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_208", "prompt": "A new law requires the USDA to approve the harvest and sale of crops from genetically modified seed even if a court has ruled against the crop as being dangerous to public safety or the environment.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_209", "prompt": "\"The ABA's own criteria for a judicial nominee call for, among other things, at least 12 years' experience in the practice of law, and they mean actual practice of law.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_210", "prompt": "Stimulus tax cuts \"began showing up in paychecks of 4.8 million Indiana households about three months ago.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_211", "prompt": "John McCain \"has threatened extinction for North Korea and sung songs about bombing Iran.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_212", "prompt": "6,400 Ohioans ... lost manufacturing jobs in the month of September.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_213", "prompt": "Says 40 years ago, the U.S. placed Texas under Voting Rights Act for failing to print ballots in Spanish.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_214", "prompt": "Nathan Deal saved the HOPE scholarship program.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_215", "prompt": "Kasichs budget raised taxes by billions, hitting businesses hard and the middle class even harder.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_216", "prompt": "The benefits that were offered to me as a congressman dont even compare to the benefits that you get as a state employee. I just experienced that myself. Theyre not nearly as good.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_217", "prompt": "Says Crist campaign website \"has eliminated all references to our Republican Party.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_218", "prompt": "Says a federal judge sanctions Tennessee birther lawyer for bringing a frivolous lawsuit.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_219", "prompt": "The Tax Foundation figures Rhode Island as the 10th highest state for state and local tax burden per capita in the country. Were the 6th worst in the country for the business tax index. Were the 3rd highest per capita in the country for all taxes.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_220", "prompt": "\"In some states, it is still legal to deny a woman coverage because she's been the victim of domestic violence.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_221", "prompt": "Says when an interviewer asked Donald Trump if he treats women with respect, Trump replied, I cant say that.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_222", "prompt": "A majority of the American people opposed the health care law when it was signed and still oppose it today.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_223", "prompt": "Says New Jerseys $1 billion horse racing industry employs 13,000 individuals and ensures the preservation of 176,000 acres of horse farmland.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_224", "prompt": "A Republican-led softening of firearms training rules means that untrained individuals would be allowed to carry guns with a state permit.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_225", "prompt": "This year, Newt Gingrich has raised as much money as Mitt Romney, Tim Pawlenty, Sarah Palin, and Mike Huckabee combined.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_226", "prompt": "Says that after she declared her candidacy for Congress, the redistricting process was manipulated to allow incumbent politicians to guarantee their re-election.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_227", "prompt": "Says he was exonerated in every single case in 1990s ethics violations charges.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_228", "prompt": "To help balance the 2011-13 budget, Gov. Scott Walker used a credit card approach that pushed over $500 million in debt onto our children and our grandchildren costing state taxpayers more than $150 million in interest.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_229", "prompt": "Says city of Portland has a one-time $22 million surplus", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_230", "prompt": "In the last six years of Ciancis administration violent crime was down in the United States. It was down in the region. It was down in Rhode Island. But it was up in Providence.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_231", "prompt": "The Every Student Succeeds Act did away basically with Common Core.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_232", "prompt": "Says Florida is a model for successful pretrial release programs.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_233", "prompt": "The Wisconsin school voucher program has no research that shows that its going to improve student learning.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_234", "prompt": "\"We spend a staggering amount of money on health care over $2-trillion and almost twice as much as any other country per person.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_235", "prompt": "Claims credit for food tax reductions that previous Democrat regimes refused to make.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_236", "prompt": "If you have ever visited Nashville or Washington D.C. you will see MANY names and initials carved into ... desks.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_237", "prompt": "By the word religion in the First Amendment, the founders meant Christianity.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_238", "prompt": "We got the highest vote count in the history of the Republican Party.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_239", "prompt": "When we look at the number of murders in the United States (in) 2009, we had 9,500 people murdered. When we look around the world, we see ... large countries, the U.K., Germany, Japan had 200 or less killed in a year.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_240", "prompt": "Says Obama opposes offshore drilling and a gas tax holiday.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_241", "prompt": "The Civil War wasnt about slavery.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_242", "prompt": "In the Obama economy ... the youth unemployment rate is double the unemployment rate for all Americans.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_243", "prompt": "Despite attention on global warming, fewer Americans carpool today to work than carpooled in 1980 and SUVs have never been a larger proportion of the vehicles being sold in this country.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_244", "prompt": "Wayne Powell has a stated position of having no objection to taking `In God We Trust off of U.S. currency.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_245", "prompt": "\"We must deal with the here and now and assure affordable fuel for America by increasing domestic production.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_246", "prompt": "In Rhode Island, 9 percent of workers use the states temporary disability insurance program each year while in New Jersey, the rate is only 3 percent.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_247", "prompt": "According to 2009 estimates, an agreement with Panama could result in almost 1,900 Florida jobs in thefirst year and about 15,000 jobs afterfive years.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_248", "prompt": "Says Mark Pryor votes with Obama 93 percent of the time.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_249", "prompt": "There are approximately 20,000 annual gun purchases in Rhode Island.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_250", "prompt": "By the year 2015 (Medicaid will) take up half our budget.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_251", "prompt": "76 percent of doctors support the use of medical marijuana", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_252", "prompt": "On how money from a possible lease of the Ohio Turnpike would be used", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_253", "prompt": "Says Charlie Crist and Missouri Rep. Todd Akin hold same abortion views. No exception except the life of the mother.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_254", "prompt": "Our (Texas) graduation rate ranks 43rd out of 50 states.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_255", "prompt": "Says three Ukrainians recently captured on a West Texas ranch are among individuals from countries that have strong terrorist ties being apprehended near the states border with Mexico.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_256", "prompt": "Says Ohio is one of just 17 states with an estate tax, and it has the lowest threshold in the nation.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_257", "prompt": "I led the fight to require the Coast Guard to buy their engines from us, not foreign companies.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_258", "prompt": "Obamacare could force thousands of volunteer fire stations to cut service or close entirely!", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_259", "prompt": "No openly gay man has ever been elected to the Georgia Legislature.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_260", "prompt": "Ive been outspent by my opponents every time Ive run for U.S. Senate.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_261", "prompt": "Says theres no proven instance where hydraulic fracking has polluted groundwater.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_262", "prompt": "Florida is one of only three states that require licenses for commercial interior designers.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_263", "prompt": "Says Rep. Charlie Bass, R-NH voted to raise his own pay eight times", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_264", "prompt": "Says Milwaukee County Executive Chris Abele eliminated sheriffs office funding for providing security for presidential and presidential campaign visits.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_265", "prompt": "Says Oregon is one of only three states that allow the use of gillnets on inland waters.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_266", "prompt": "Weve added, in the last eight years, $4 trillion of debt to the nations obligations.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_267", "prompt": "Obamacare cuts seniors Medicare.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_268", "prompt": "One international flight a day in a wide-bodied jet ... one flight daily generates $150 million a year and approximately 2,300 jobs.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_269", "prompt": "By spring 2014, parents of 60,000 students in New York state had refused to let them take the Common Core Tests.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_270", "prompt": "The average family not in the top 10 percent makes less money today than they were making a generation ago.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_271", "prompt": "On President Barack Obamas stimulus", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_272", "prompt": "Expanding the sale of full-strength beer and wine to grocery stores isgood for everybody.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_273", "prompt": "Earth has not warmed for the last 17 years.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_274", "prompt": "There are only four countries in the world that ... legalize abortion after five months -- China, North Korea, Canada and the U.S.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_275", "prompt": "Says Charlie Crist raised taxes on the middle class by $2.2 billion.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_276", "prompt": "Says 600,000 to 700,000 government workers have been laid off in the last year and a half", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_277", "prompt": "In altered photo, says Barack Obama wants more of Texans private data via health care.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_278", "prompt": "More Texans have new jobs today than the entire population of Fort Worth.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_279", "prompt": "In Europe, church attendance rates (are) in the single digits because churches are supported by taxes.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_280", "prompt": "Says five studies show his tax plan can cut rates and still bring the same revenue without raising taxes on the middle class.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_281", "prompt": "Says some [states] with the largest reductions in crime have also lowered their prison population.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_282", "prompt": "Says, when this governor came to office, he had (an) 11 billion dollar - I call it mismanagement deficit.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_283", "prompt": "\"Sen. Obama has always had a 100 percent prochoice rating.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_284", "prompt": "The vast majority of minimum wage workers get a raise within a year.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_285", "prompt": "Barack Obama got more campaign contributions from Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac \"than any other member of Congress, except for the Democratic chairmen of the committee that oversees them.\"", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_286", "prompt": "Says ending the direct payment farm subsidy program could save up to $28.4 billion over ten years that could be used to reduce the deficit.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_287", "prompt": "If we choose Obamacare expansion, 600,000 will lose eligibility for their subsidies, of which 257,000 would be forced into Medicaid.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_288", "prompt": "The pope and Donald Trump and Tammy Baldwin all agree on eliminating the carried-interest tax break.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_289", "prompt": "Says Chuck Hagels nomination as defense secretary has been publicly celebrated by the Iranian government.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_290", "prompt": "Dan Webster supports privatization of Social Security, deep cuts in Social Security.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_291", "prompt": "A gas tax holiday \"would at best provide 30 cents a day for three months for a grand total of $28.\"", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_292", "prompt": "Says I worked with our Mayor and other commissioners to help save the school year when a budget crisis in Salem threatened to cut four weeks of the school year, including negotiating with teachers to work for free.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_293", "prompt": "Says Barack Obama has the legal authority to let in really however many refugees he wants, from whatever country.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_294", "prompt": "Austin school district teachers are the lowest paid of any urban Texas district and the lowest paid of any surrounding school district.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_295", "prompt": "Congress is on a five-week vacation.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_296", "prompt": "U.S. Senate candidate Jack Kingston requested more earmarks than any other GA Congressman and all GA GOP members combined.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_297", "prompt": "A recent Gallup poll found that 72 percent of Americans and 56 percent of Democrats say the biggest threat to our nations security is big government.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_298", "prompt": "Remember that developers are forced to use the 195 land union contractors, so tap an extra $10 million into any construction project.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_299", "prompt": "Michelle Obama ordered $400 worth of lobster and caviar at a New York hotel.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_300", "prompt": "\"Since that famous day in February where the governor campaigned with Barack Obama on behalf of the stimulus program, 211,000 Floridians have lost their jobs.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_301", "prompt": "More Americans have died from guns in the United States since 1968 than on battlefields of all the wars in American history.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_302", "prompt": "Says President Barack Obama is a socialist.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_303", "prompt": "Under former President George W. Bushs administration while the population in that period grew by 10 percent, the number of jobs in the nation grew by 1 percent.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_304", "prompt": "A private school tax break in the Wisconsin state budget is the most generous in the nation.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_305", "prompt": "Members of the military dont contribute toward their pension.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_306", "prompt": "Russia has tremendous numbers of nuclear warheads 1,800, by the way where they expanded, and we didnt.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_307", "prompt": "ISIS leader Abu Bakr al Baghdadi was released by Obama in 2009.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_308", "prompt": "In 2011, Alabama and Massachusetts passed legislation allowing non-citizens who are legal residents to vote in state and local elections.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_309", "prompt": "No other country has a constitutional right like the Second Amendment.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_310", "prompt": "Obamacare will question your sex life.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_311", "prompt": "Teachers are working their third consecutive year -- some longer than that -- without salary increases.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_312", "prompt": "One person has been fired at the Veterans Administration for withholding services.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_313", "prompt": "Robert Hurt supported a bill that helped the uranium industry after taking contributions from the industry and because his father had a stake in it.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_314", "prompt": "As secretary of the Department of Energy under former President Bill Clinton, \"I created reserves of home heating oil.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_315", "prompt": "TheAffordable Care Actalters the sensible doctor-patient-relationship-centered health care program ... we see today.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_316", "prompt": "Here in Wisconsin, weve put in previous budgets more money into mental health services than any governor has in the last 25 years.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_317", "prompt": "John Kitzhaber created 128,000 new jobs while governor.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_318", "prompt": "McCain is \"selectively editing Joe Biden's words...Biden actually said about Barack Obama: 'They're gonna find out this guy's got steel in his spine.'\"", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_319", "prompt": "Mitt Romney ... gave you government health care that is now bankrupting the state of Massachusetts.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_320", "prompt": "Says the Congressional Budget Office said if youre going to buy your own policy with these (health care) exchanges youll be paying 10 percent more ... about $2,100 more for a family.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_321", "prompt": "Health care reform plans being consided in Congress \"will finally reduce the costs of health care.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_322", "prompt": "Forty-five percent of Americans went without needed care because of costs in 2007.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_323", "prompt": "Wisconsin is dead last in the Midwest for job creation.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_324", "prompt": "AIG has fully repaid the federal government plus a profit of more than $22 billion.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_325", "prompt": "Every president since Franklin Delano Roosevelt has had fast-track trade authority.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_326", "prompt": "Seven of Americas 10 wealthiest counties are in the Washington, D.C., area.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_327", "prompt": "Our last budget committed the highest level of need-based financial aid in state history.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_328", "prompt": "For every one job created under the Obama administration, 75 people went on food stamps.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_329", "prompt": "We have killed lots of innocent people in the state of Texas.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_330", "prompt": "Social Security is a Ponzi scheme.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_331", "prompt": "Only 18 percent of jobs are accessible by transit for metro Atlanta residents. 33 percent for those living in the city.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_332", "prompt": "The health care law reduces the number of uninsured in America by 3 percent for how much money? $2 trillion.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_333", "prompt": "Starting in 2011, \"you will be required to pay taxes\" on \"the value of whatever health insurance you are given by the company.\"", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_334", "prompt": "Seventy bills [Kendrick Meek] authored, not one of them has passed.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_335", "prompt": "There is no clinical evidence that vaccinating healthcare workers protects patients.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_336", "prompt": "Says Alex Jones said that the victims of the Sandy Hook massacre were child actors and no one was actually killed there.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_337", "prompt": "If you count United States airstrikes against ISIS, 75 percent of those combat missions return to base without having fired a weapon.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_338", "prompt": "Individuals with mental illnesses die an average of 25 years earlier than those without a mental illness.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_339", "prompt": "Sen. Joe Biden, the ranking member of the Foreign Relations Committee, recommended partitioning Iraq into three separate entities.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_340", "prompt": "Claims that former Sen. Tom Daschle said, \"Seniors should be more accepting of the conditions that come with age instead of treating them.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_341", "prompt": "\"There's only four senators senior to me ... there's still 44 older than me.\"", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_342", "prompt": "\"The fact is, in the past year we have had more tax cuts than almost any time in our nation's history.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_343", "prompt": "African-American youth unemployment is 51 percent. Hispanic youth unemployment is 36 percent.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_344", "prompt": "Says President Barack Obama promised he would cut the deficit in half, but instead will at least double it.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_345", "prompt": "California has the sixth largest economy on planet Earth.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_346", "prompt": "When Tallahassee politicians and bureaucrats tried to run our schools, Ive stood up to them to protect local control.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_347", "prompt": "Scott Maddox has run \"losing campaigns for 3 of Florida's 4 available cabinet positions.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_348", "prompt": "Black people kill more black people every six months than the KKK did in 86 years.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_349", "prompt": "Under Maggie Hassans leadership, we increased state spending in the middle of the great recession by 24 percent leading up to and following it.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_350", "prompt": "Florida Democrats put my Social Security number and my wifes Employment Identification Number in a mail piece.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_351", "prompt": "The United States has the highest incarceration rate in the world.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_352", "prompt": "FBI confirms evidence of huge underground Clinton sex network.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_353", "prompt": "[A] 2009 USDA study found that 87 percent of chicken carcasses tested positive for generic E. coli ... just prior to packaging.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_354", "prompt": "\"The Florida Legislature raised taxes and fees by almost $2 billion\" in the 2009 session.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_355", "prompt": "Says We do about 300 investigations a year into housing discrimination and in recent years have put about $150,000 of damages into the pockets of individuals who have been treated unfairly.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_356", "prompt": "For the second quarter in a row, my campaign has raised more money than any other challenger in the nation and brought our fundraising total to over $800,000.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_357", "prompt": "$16 trillion (the national debt) in $1 bills would cover the entire state of Ohio nearly 1.5 times.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_358", "prompt": "Says about 100,000 kids in this country leave their home state and go to another state to be educated. Out of that 100,000 young people, 30,000 of them are from New Jersey, by far the largest amount.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_359", "prompt": "Says U.S. Rep. Michael McCaul is the sixth-richest person in Congress.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_360", "prompt": "Millions could lose their health care coverage and be forced into a government pool under the new health care law.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_361", "prompt": "\"The founders advised non-interventionism.\"", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_362", "prompt": "No other public or private business in America except for the U.S. Postal Service must fund 100 percent of employee retirement and retirement health costs in advance.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_363", "prompt": "Since 2007, Texas has gained 440,000 people while Maryland has lost 20,000.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_364", "prompt": "Last month, 44 of the 50 states saw an increase in the unemployment rate.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_365", "prompt": "The Hyde Amendmentlanguage was in the (human trafficking) bill. The Democratic sponsor admits it was in the bill, and she voted for it.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_366", "prompt": "Tim Pawlenty has cut education funding in Minnesota. Classrooms are overcrowded. Districts have gone to four-day school weeks.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_367", "prompt": "Says U.S. Senate opponent Tommy Thompson personally made over $3 million from a federal contract granted to his healthcare company, but left 9/11 first responders without the care they were promised.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_368", "prompt": "[T]he Georgia Dome has returned $10 billion in economic impact to the state of Georgia.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_369", "prompt": "Seniors with coverage under Medicare Advantage will give up \"more than their share\" because of health care reform", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_370", "prompt": "Our jobless rate, our unemployment rate, is the lowest of all of the big cities in New Jersey.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_371", "prompt": "Says Texas economy is about 30 percent larger than Australias.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_372", "prompt": "The Mormon religion has \"a plan that will see the Constitution thrown out and replaced by a theocracy.\"", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_373", "prompt": "This president spends 30 times as much money on global warming research as he does on weather forecasting and warning.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_374", "prompt": "Every time somebody new gets the Ebola virus, it mutates.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_375", "prompt": "More than 250 (voter registration) groups, ranging across the entire political spectrum, have filed with the state and are registering voters right now.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_376", "prompt": "Says a car driving former University of Missouri System President Tim Wolfe ran through the students, hit one of them at the MU Homecoming Parade.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_377", "prompt": "By the time I left the State Department, economic growth was up and opium production was down in Afghanistan, while infant mortality declined and school enrollment rose by more than sevenfold.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_378", "prompt": "Says Donald Trump says climate change is a hoax invented by the Chinese.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_379", "prompt": "The financial services regulatory bill \"will end taxpayer bailouts.\"", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_380", "prompt": "Under the plan, for the first five years your employer not only has to keep the coverage, but you can't migrate to the public plan.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_381", "prompt": "For every extra year that a girl stays in secondary school, her chance of getting infected with HIV/AIDS decreases by half.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_382", "prompt": "Ninety percent of the people in Arkansas still love Bill Clinton.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_383", "prompt": "Right now, Im polling at about 8 percent against Barack Obama and Mitt Romney.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_384", "prompt": "Says that under President John F. Kennedy, government took up 27 percent of the economy, and today it consumes 37 percent.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_385", "prompt": "Republicans have proposed dozens of (health care) solutions designed to help control costs and improve quality.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_386", "prompt": "Many of the 9/11 conspirators came from the Muslim Brotherhood, including Osama bin Laden, Ayman Zawahiri and Khalid Sheikh Mohammed.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_387", "prompt": "If you rent a U-Haul to move your company, it costs twice as much to go from San Francisco to Austin than the other way around, because you cant find enough trucks to flee the Golden State.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_388", "prompt": "Maggie Hassan missed nearly every university system board meeting.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_389", "prompt": "Says Patrick Murphy hasnt passed a single bill out of committee.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_390", "prompt": "The Fourth Amendment was what we fought the Revolution over. John Adams said it was the spark that led to our war for independence.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_391", "prompt": "The Republican Party lost 1.1 million registered voters since 2008. The Democratic Party lost 1.2 million registered voters (while) voter registration in the Libertarian Party rose 8 percent.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_392", "prompt": "Says Hillary Clinton had an undercover nurse with her at the Sept. 11 memorial ceremony in New York.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_393", "prompt": "Says federal regulations adopted in 2011 increased the cost of each vehicle for his business by $10,000.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_394", "prompt": "President Barack Obama reduced the cost of prescription drugs for nearly 3.6 million Americans in 2011.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_395", "prompt": "We have a $2 trillion to $3 trillion infrastructure deficit. Weve got work that needs to get done. Weve got people that want to go to work.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_396", "prompt": "Denali is the Kenyan word for black power.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_397", "prompt": "She led the fight to stop health insurance rate hikes and saved Rhode Island families over $150 million.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_398", "prompt": "More than 50 percent of those people getting minimum wage in this state are high school students.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_399", "prompt": "Weve had the private sector more than double the investment that was made by the public sector at Quonset Business Park.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_400", "prompt": "The federal government owns 30 percent of the land in the 50 states, or about 650 million acres.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_401", "prompt": "When Disney was looking to build Disney World, they came to Miami and we told Disney to take a hike.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_402", "prompt": "If you don't count illegal aliens, people who qualify for other insurance, and people who make more than $75,000 a year, it leaves about 15 million people who are uninsured.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_403", "prompt": "Says abill he vetoed to give driver licenses to certain immigrants known as Dreamers would havechanged nothing.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_404", "prompt": "The list of voters that North Carolina Republicans tried to purge was two-thirds black and Democratic.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_405", "prompt": "On supporting the budget proposed by Rep. Paul Ryan", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_406", "prompt": "In Georgia, hard-earned lottery dollars are doled out to the scion[s] of wealthy families.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_407", "prompt": "A Trump television ad shows Mexicans swarming over our southern border.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_408", "prompt": "Says businesses pay roughly 60 percent of taxes in Texas.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_409", "prompt": "Says the federal government could save $175,587 by eliminating a study of the connection between cocaine and risky sex habits of the Japanese quail.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_410", "prompt": "Donald Trump is appealing as much to Democrats as he is to Republicans.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_411", "prompt": "When we took office, let me remind you, there was virtually no international pressure on Iran.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_412", "prompt": "The administration has issued rules for $1 abortions in ObamaCare and requires all persons enrolled in insurance plans that include elective abortion coverage to pay an abortion premium.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_413", "prompt": "Republicans went out of the way to praise (Eric) Holders nomination. ... Not a single Republican senator opposed Eric Holders nomination.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_414", "prompt": "In Rhode Island, Nearly 9 percent of covered employees go out on short term disability every year, with an average outage from work of almost 12 weeks each.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_415", "prompt": "After the oil spill, Congressman Adam Putnam \"doubled down saying all energy sources, including oil drilling in the Gulf, should be considered just days after the oil spill started.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_416", "prompt": "As the CEO of eBay, \"Whitman started a separate division that only sells porn.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_417", "prompt": "The number of people in Atlanta dying from HIV and AIDS declined 59 percent between 2004 and 2012.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_418", "prompt": "The largest number of gamblers are from the poorest segments of the population.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_419", "prompt": "Its actually easier for the United States to get flight manifests from E.U. nations than it is for E.U. nations to get them from their own neighbors, thanks to an agreement the U.S. negotiated when I was secretary of state.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_420", "prompt": "On average, women make 77 cents for every dollar men make.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_421", "prompt": "We are now eighth in the nation in job creation . . . we are No. 1 in the Midwest.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_422", "prompt": "By 2009, dozens of senior terrorists had been taken off the battlefield by drones.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_423", "prompt": "Says Sen. John McCain has taken more money from Wall Street than any other sitting senator.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_424", "prompt": "Says that in 2007, Oregon ranked 25th -- or 7th from the bottom -- in percentage of children with untreated decay compared to 32 other states with similar data.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_425", "prompt": "The health care bills will be mandated spending. You cant cut it, regardless of the budget circumstances.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_426", "prompt": "Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walkers budget okays disposing of unclaimed pound dogs to university research facilities.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_427", "prompt": "Says over 1 million signatures were submitted in attempt to recall Gov. Scott Walker.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_428", "prompt": "Says his plan would cut taxes without increasing the deficit.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_429", "prompt": "Harry Reid has voted to give illegals Social Security benefits even for the time they were here illegally.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_430", "prompt": "Says U.S. House opponent Michael Williams does not live in and has never voted in the congressional district hes seeking to represent.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_431", "prompt": "The Obama White House is renaming Christmas trees \"holiday trees.\"", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_432", "prompt": "The payday loan industry does not exist in a state like Minnesota.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_433", "prompt": "Says Donald Trump is the first person running for president, Republican or Democrat, who refused to say that he would respect the results of this election.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_434", "prompt": "Republican-leaning states get more in federal dollars than they pay in taxes.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_435", "prompt": "At least 10 ISIS fighters have been caught coming across the Mexican border in Texas and there are dozens more that did not get caught by the Border Patrol.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_436", "prompt": "We have 33,000 people a year who die from guns.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_437", "prompt": "Of all cities in the United States with more than 100,000 people, Providence is the 183rd safest.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_438", "prompt": "\"I'm proud of the fact that I've raised more money from small donors than anybody else, and that we're getting $25, $50, $100 donations, and we've done very well doing it that way.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_439", "prompt": "In 1940, only 7 percentof Germans were Nazis.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_440", "prompt": "A request for \"an increase in troops sat on desks in this White House (during the presidency of George W. Bush), including the vice president's, for more than eight months, a resource request filled by President Obama in March.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_441", "prompt": "Prices are going up. Unemployment is continuing to go up.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_442", "prompt": "Ive either balanced every budget or we turned back a surplus.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_443", "prompt": "If you are a member of union, your median weekly income is roughly $200 more than if you are a nonunion member, and that doesnt include benefits.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_444", "prompt": "President Barack Obamas Fiscal Year 2013 budget proposal couldnt get support from either party in the House or the Senate.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_445", "prompt": "The fastest-growing part of the Pentagons budget are health care expenses.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_446", "prompt": "The deficit was on track to top $1 trillion the year I took office.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_447", "prompt": "Says Oregon ranks 43rd in education.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_448", "prompt": "Weve seen in this last year tremendous things happening, including our unemployment rate come down 2 percentage points.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_449", "prompt": "Proposed tax changes are a handout to BP.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_450", "prompt": "The 2011 Rebuild America Jobs Act would have cost the average American family $1,000 a year while making no significant impact to fix our infrastructure and roads.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_451", "prompt": "Pinnacle Overlook in Southwest Virginia is closer to eight other state capitals than to Richmond.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_452", "prompt": "Says GOP Congressional candidate Scott Jones wants to build a wall. He wants to round people up and deport folks.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_453", "prompt": "Rhode Island has the most burdensome level of health-insurance mandates in the nation.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_454", "prompt": "Currently, the intelligence community can collect business records on law-abiding Americans who have no connection to terrorism.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_455", "prompt": "Says Hillary Clinton gave up 20 percent of Americas uranium supply to Russia.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_456", "prompt": "Says as a result of the national health care reform, the Congressional Budget Office says we save $250 million over the first 10 years. Over the next 10 years, we save $1.2 trillion in savings in terms of health care.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_457", "prompt": "Women in Ohio earn on average 77 cents for every dollar earned by a man.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_458", "prompt": "We had the biggest drop of the rate of unemployment (in)all but 4 states.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_459", "prompt": "Wisconsin does not have a deficit. Thanks to Republican reforms, the 2014 budget will begin with a $443 million surplus.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_460", "prompt": "Cell phone numbers go public this month.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_461", "prompt": "Six justices on the U.S. Supreme Court have been confirmed in presidential election years since 1912.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_462", "prompt": "Its a good sign for Obamacare that in California, the proportion of kids who are signing up is the proportion of kids in the population.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_463", "prompt": "After I had resigned or announced my resignation, I abolished -- I prohibited pay-to-play for people that had county or state contracts.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_464", "prompt": "John McCain \"said publicly that Hillary Clinton would make a good president.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_465", "prompt": "Says Texas retained the right to have a navy when it joined the United States.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_466", "prompt": "In Romneys first budget (in Massachusetts), he cut $248.7 million from K-12 education.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_467", "prompt": "Says some Wisconsin state employee contracts gave some employees $4 for bringing in their own lunch.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_468", "prompt": "Under Rick Scott, there has been a historic $20 billion in funds for education.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_469", "prompt": "Says that before Rick Perry became governor, only 4 percent of our total labor force was a minimum wage job ... Today, that number has more than doubled (to) 9.5 percent.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_470", "prompt": "Says New Jersey Devils managing partner Jeff Vanderbeek froze all those monies during the toughest years in 08-09 and refused to give the charitable dollars that he was required to give by the contract.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_471", "prompt": "Says Ohio has 77 job training programs spread across 13 state agencies.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_472", "prompt": "@realDonaldTrump is coming to San Antonio, which is 60% Mexican-AMERICAN.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_473", "prompt": "More than any Republican governor in the 2014 elections, I took a higher percentage of the Republican voteand yet I also carried independents by 12 points.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_474", "prompt": "(Deborah) Ross defends those who want to burn the American flag, and even called efforts to ban flag-burning ridiculous, yet refused to help a disabled veteran fly the flag.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_475", "prompt": "Says U.S. Senate candidate Eric Hovde has no problem with raising taxes.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_476", "prompt": "Voting in the wrong precinct led to over 14,000 registered voters statewide to lose their vote in 2008.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_477", "prompt": "U.S. Rep. Phil Gingrey wants public schools to teach women to stay in their place.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_478", "prompt": "In 2009 Hillary Clinton was at the State Department working with U.S. corporations to pressure Haiti not to raise the minimum wage to 61 cents an hour from 24 cents.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_479", "prompt": "Of six Rhode Island tax-credit programs worth about $35 million, three companies got 90 percent of that -- CVS and two companies not even located in the state of Rhode Island.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_480", "prompt": "High school students arrested on campus are twice as likely not to graduate and four times less likely to graduate if theyve appeared in court.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_481", "prompt": "The minimum wage has risen $2.35 in the last two years. Thats 31 percent.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_482", "prompt": "92 million Americans arent working.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_483", "prompt": "Says a highway was closed in El Paso because of bullets flying across the border.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_484", "prompt": "Says a Republican-drawn map of proposed U.S. House districts for Texas gerrymanders more than nine million Latinos in Texas to make sure that we have no more electoral opportunity than we did in 1991.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_485", "prompt": "Obama's wife said her goal in life was to put the black community \"first and foremost.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_486", "prompt": "We were not, I repeat, were not told that waterboarding or any of these other enhanced interrogation methods were used.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_487", "prompt": "97 percent of the work that Planned Parenthood does is about mammograms and preventative health.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_488", "prompt": "Says she oversaw an audit that won the city $2 million in franchise fees.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_489", "prompt": "African-Americans are more likely to be arrested by police and sentenced to longer prison terms for doing the same thing that whites do.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_490", "prompt": "There are actual cities like Birmingham, England, that are totally Muslim where non-Muslims just simply dont go in.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_491", "prompt": "In Senate Bill 5, there is this new method of evaluating teachers. Youre also going to be rated on what the parents think of you and they can send questionnaires and surveys home to parents.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_492", "prompt": "A record number of Hispanics were elected to the U.S House of Representatives...", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_493", "prompt": "President Obamas health care law says when you sell your house now you have to pay a 3.8 percent tax.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_494", "prompt": "Says Josh Mandel opposed federal loans to the auto industry.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_495", "prompt": "Says President Obama waited two weeks to call the attack in Libya terror.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_496", "prompt": "We cut property taxes by one-third in the state of Texas while Ive been governor.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_497", "prompt": "F: The grade given to Florida for college affordability under Jeb Bushs leadership.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_498", "prompt": "Twice as much (federal) money is going back to Hawaii, Virginia and Alaska than is coming home to Oregon.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_499", "prompt": "Amendment 4 will reduce Floridas economic output by $34 billion annually.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_500", "prompt": "Florida remains the top travel destination across the world.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_501", "prompt": "Under Mayor Cicilline, [Providence] was a sanctuary city.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_502", "prompt": "The U.S. military is in 130 countries. We have 900 bases around the world.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_503", "prompt": "Says the giant African land snail carries human meningitis.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_504", "prompt": "RNC version of a Hillary Clinton valentine: \"Roses are red, violets are blue, I'll raise your taxes and there is nothing you can do.\"", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_505", "prompt": "The Republican plan for tax cuts is to give each millionaire -- the top 1 percent of income in this country -- $83,347 a year in tax cuts.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_506", "prompt": "Nearly one in four people in their prime working years are not working.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_507", "prompt": "In Wisconsin, more than 300,000 people have some kind of addictive gambling problem, whether its pathological or what wed categorize as a problem gambler.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_508", "prompt": "90 percent of all pain medications are prescribed in the United States.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_509", "prompt": "The two worst counties for (Medicaid) fraud in the country -- not state -- are Dade and Broward county.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_510", "prompt": "Says President Barack Obama is trying to pack the D.C. Circuit Court of Appeals.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_511", "prompt": "Says Jon Huntsman supports changes in Medicare that would deny guaranteed benefits to 980,000 New Hampshire residents.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_512", "prompt": "Undocumented workers crossing the border right now is at a 12-year low.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_513", "prompt": "A couple of hundred American cities are infested by members of the Mexican cartels.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_514", "prompt": "\"Today and every day, an estimated 14,000 Americans will lose their health insurance coverage.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_515", "prompt": "On raising taxes.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_516", "prompt": "More than 70,000 job openings are listed on a state jobs website.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_517", "prompt": "\"She stood by ground zero workers who sacrificed their health after so many sacrificed their lives and kept standing till this administration took action.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_518", "prompt": "Says Bernie Sanders health care plan would empower Republicangovernors to take away Medicaid,to take away health insurance for low-income and middle-income working Americans.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_519", "prompt": "The Islamic State just built a hotel in Syria.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_520", "prompt": "Says Hillary Clinton makes more per hour at a speaking gig than the average CEO does in a year.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_521", "prompt": "Pat Toomey still supports privatizing Social Security.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_522", "prompt": "\"As has been noted by many observers, including Bill Clinton's former secretary of labor, my plan does more than anybody to reduce costs.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_523", "prompt": "Says New Jerseys prison system is 61 percent African-American even though our state is just 13 percent black.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_524", "prompt": "Says the American public overwhelmingly opposed Democratic-steered health care plan.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_525", "prompt": "Says Donald Trumps polling numbers show that hes the highest with Hispanics that any Republican has ever been.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_526", "prompt": "On using the Strategic Petroleum Reserve.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_527", "prompt": "Were spending millions for each individual held at Guantanamo Bay, Cuba.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_528", "prompt": "Wendy Davis is fighting to bring ... Bloomberg-style gun control to Texas.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_529", "prompt": "Its possible that non-citizen voters were responsible for Obamas 2008 victory in North Carolina.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_530", "prompt": "While 9,000 state employees were added to the states payroll, Oregons revenue forecasts dropped by more than $4 billion.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_531", "prompt": "Health proposal would create a \"40% tax on health care benefits of middle-class workers.\"", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_532", "prompt": "\"I don't answer hypotheticals.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_533", "prompt": "During Obamas first five years as president, black unemployment increased 42 percent. During Reagans presidency, black unemployment dropped 20 percent.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_534", "prompt": "Says Delta Air Lines has once again broken a promise they made to me and to the people of Memphis.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_535", "prompt": "Says he helped to draft parts of the Dodd-Frank Wall Street reform bill.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_536", "prompt": "Some doctors say Ebola can be transmitted through the air by a sneeze or some cough.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_537", "prompt": "In 2007, Ed Gillespie was paid $300,000 to be the frontman for a coalition that made the individual mandate the centerpiece of its health reform plan.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_538", "prompt": "This years state budget and my spending proposal for Fiscal Year 2016 represent an infusion of more than $1 billion in additional money for K-12 education.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_539", "prompt": "Mark Kirk: Lied about going to war. Opposed middle class tax cuts. And said unemployments not that big an issue.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_540", "prompt": "I did not play any role in bringing the company to RI as did others in government. I was tasked with handling the legislation affecting the company by my superiors.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_541", "prompt": "When it comes to the state deficit, Wisconsin is proportionally in as much trouble as the State of California.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_542", "prompt": "Israel has seen a 90 percent reduction in terrorist attacks that it attributes to building a 500-mile fence.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_543", "prompt": "Bin Laden had declared war against Pakistan.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_544", "prompt": "Congresswoman Ros-Lehtinen has long record of voting against VA backlog fixes.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_545", "prompt": "In annual surveys of Rhode Island communities that receive Drug Free community grants, many report that more than 50 percent of youth surveyed do not think daily marijuana use poses any serious risk of harm.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_546", "prompt": "A gun background check is futile. Something like 42 (people during the) last year were prosecuted for trying to buy a gun with a criminal record out of 11 million.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_547", "prompt": "If Rhode Island raises the meal and beverage tax to 10 percent, it would be the fourth-highest in the nation.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_548", "prompt": "Massachusetts under Gov. Mitt Romney initially ranked last among states in job growth, but by the end of his governorship, we were in the middle of the pack.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_549", "prompt": "Georgia lawmakers fuel up for the session by feasting on wild hogs.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_550", "prompt": "Says MarkKirk called for the mass arrest of 18,000 African Americans andwas apparently fine with Trumps #StillTooRacist call for mass deportation.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_551", "prompt": "Says $500 billion in Medicare cuts are coming.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_552", "prompt": "Says Gov. Mike Pence and Rep. Mike Coffman take the same positions on a number of things... Coffman and Pence oppose equal rights for LGBT Americans.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_553", "prompt": "Says Hillary Clinton opposed an individual mandate and favored an employer mandate back in 1993.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_554", "prompt": "Says Chris Christie created this new category where you could get laid off and just be totally denied unemployment benefits forever.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_555", "prompt": "Next year, you will be mandated by federal law to get rid of your existing light bulbs.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_556", "prompt": "Every day, a black name resume is 50 percent less likely to get responded to than a white nameresume.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_557", "prompt": "Ohio Director of Job Creation Mark Kvamme just clawed back about $900,000 from companies that made promises and they didnt keep them.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_558", "prompt": "Says There are now Occupy Wall Street camps in hundreds of cities across the United States.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_559", "prompt": "The Trump Winery near Charlottesville, Va. is the largest winery on the East Coast.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_560", "prompt": "The health care law was a 2,733-page bill! . . . No amendments!", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_561", "prompt": "Says Every time the Legislature suspended the kicker, most recently the corporate kicker in 2007, Salem spent every penny and failed to stabilize the states revenues.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_562", "prompt": "Says Hillary Clinton has even deleted this record of total support (for the Trans-Pacific Partnership trade agreement) from her book.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_563", "prompt": "Said state insurance commissioner candidate Ralph Hudgens fights hard to strip women of life-saving coverage such as mammograms.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_564", "prompt": "Right now, we only keep 50 percent of Georgia Techs graduates.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_565", "prompt": "In Texas, we teach both creationism and evolution in our public schools.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_566", "prompt": "Says Philando Castile had been stopped by police 40 or 50 times before that fatal incident.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_567", "prompt": "Says Tommy Thompson pushed such strict laws that abortion providers faced potential life imprisonment and women were forced to cross state lines in order to receive attention for life-threatening issues.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_568", "prompt": "\"The Democrats in the Senate and some members of Congress defended what Fannie and Freddie were doing. They resisted any change.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_569", "prompt": "If you look at our tax mix, the share of corporate revenues as a percentage of our overall revenue mix has declined by about half over the last 30 years.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_570", "prompt": "The Obama administration called Bashar Assad a reformer when he was turning his Russian-provided guns on his own people.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_571", "prompt": "Says with Jon Corzine, its the first time, I think, in history where a former Senator has been subpoenaed to testify before his former colleagues.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_572", "prompt": "Opponents of Section 5 (of the Voting Rights Act) complain of state expense, yet their only cost is the paper, postage and manpower required to send copies of legislation to the federal government for review.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_573", "prompt": "We are the only industrialized nation that relies heavily on a for-profit medical insurance industry to provide basic health care.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_574", "prompt": "Thanks to Washington, nearly everyone will pay more in taxes in 2013. Somehow people think its just the wealthy. Its not.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_575", "prompt": "Says Hillary Clinton and millennials have the same positions on climate change, abortion rights, immigration reform, gay rights and college affordability. Donald Trump doesnt.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_576", "prompt": "Texas is growing twice as fast as the rest of the country.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_577", "prompt": "One-third of all bank tellers (are) on public assistance.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_578", "prompt": "Says a university survey concluded his Massachusetts administration had more women in senior leadership positions than any other state in America.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_579", "prompt": "On the mosque near ground zero.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_580", "prompt": "Barack Obama will \"raise Social Security taxes.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_581", "prompt": "Says for the first time in the history of the United States, the government cut taxes during wartime", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_582", "prompt": "\"I negotiated open borders to let fleeing refugees into safety from Kosovo.\"", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_583", "prompt": "One estimate says there may be three times as much oil in the United States as there is in Saudi Arabia.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_584", "prompt": "There have been multiple media reports about (Donald Trumps) business dealings with the mob, with the mafia.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_585", "prompt": "Says she voted against the Medicare Part D prescription drug program because it was unfunded.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_586", "prompt": "Most federal employees do not have collective bargaining for benefits, nor for pay.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_587", "prompt": "Says he has \"the most impressive education record\" of the Republican candidates.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_588", "prompt": "Says Measure 11 is one of the most significant reasons for decrease in violent crime.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_589", "prompt": "A strong majority of Americans support the Keystone XL pipeline.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_590", "prompt": "AARP is endorsing the health care reform bill.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_591", "prompt": "All four on Mount Rushmore, they were all independents at one critical point in their career.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_592", "prompt": "When Roy Barnes was governor, \"Georgia created 235,000 jobs.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_593", "prompt": "Almost 95 percent of all (Planned Parenthood) pregnancy services were abortions.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_594", "prompt": "You cant build a Christian church in Saudi Arabia.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_595", "prompt": "Texas is one of only a handful of states that does not have an equal pay law.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_596", "prompt": "The WIC program is an incredibly cost effective program, serving nearly 10 million Americans each year and costing less than $100 per person. In my district, more than 18 percent of residents suffer from food insecurity and depend on WIC to make ends meet.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_597", "prompt": "Our debt is already bigger than our economy.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_598", "prompt": "Quarterbacks won the (Super Bowl) MVP more than 50 percent of the time.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_599", "prompt": "Paul Ryan cut embassy security in his budget by $300 million below what we asked for.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_600", "prompt": "Says that since lawmakers acted, we have 130 new businesses across Texas doing helicopter hog hunts.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_601", "prompt": "The Obama administration notified Poland and the Czech Republic about cancellation of major missile-defense facilities \"at the last minute in midnight phone calls.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_602", "prompt": "For the amount of money Hillary Clinton would like to spend on refugees, we could rebuild every inner city in America.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_603", "prompt": "\"John wasn't this raging populist four years ago\" when he ran for president.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_604", "prompt": "Health care reform legislation is likely to mandate free sex change surgeries.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_605", "prompt": "Nothing in the Constitution explicitly guarantees our right to vote.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_606", "prompt": "Every year, more than $40 million are leaving Missouri for the Lone Star State.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_607", "prompt": "Says Jeb Bush flip-flop-flip(ped) on immigration.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_608", "prompt": "An image in a ChrisAbele TV ad depicts wealthy citizens who would benefit from a lake created by the controversial Estabrook Dam.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_609", "prompt": "In the 100 days since its passage, the economic stimulus has \"saved or created nearly 150,000 jobs.\"", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_610", "prompt": "Congress is bewildered at the scope and reach of our spying apparatus but in 2008 and 2012 explicitly rejected an amendment calling for more disclosure.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_611", "prompt": "All Aboard Florida is receiving millions in Florida taxpayer dollars.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_612", "prompt": "As executive director of the Democratic Party of Virginia there were 300 people on my payroll in 2008.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_613", "prompt": "Weve got to find 2 billion gallons (of water per day) between now and 2025.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_614", "prompt": "We have over 300 state agencies. Forty-five of those agencies are related to health care.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_615", "prompt": "Every day, 34 Americans are murdered with guns.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_616", "prompt": "Says under his budget-repair bill, collective bargaining is fully intact.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_617", "prompt": "Obama wants to increase the size of government by 23 percent.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_618", "prompt": "Less than 10 percent of President Barack Obamas Cabinet members have private-sector experience.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_619", "prompt": "The highest economic growth decade was the 1960s. Income tax rates were 90 percent.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_620", "prompt": "There are only about 10 people in the United States Senate who have any real business experience.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_621", "prompt": "Says he has supported George Bush more than I have Barack Obama.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_622", "prompt": "Says he and Bernie Sanders have very similar views on trade", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_623", "prompt": "A bill backed by Sean Duffy and other House Republicans could actually require the Internal Revenue Service to conduct audits of rape victims who get an abortion.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_624", "prompt": "Like Marco Rubio, Sen. Barack Obama had one of the worst attendance records in the Senate.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_625", "prompt": "\"Jeff Greene only moved from California to Florida in the last two years. In fact, he would not legally be allowed to run for any other statewide office because he has not lived here long enough to meet the residency requirement.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_626", "prompt": "Were now the No. 1 producer of oil in the world. Weve surpassed Saudi Arabia.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_627", "prompt": "\"Mayor Giuliani made New York City what's known as a 'sanctuary city,' where illegal aliens were allowed to come. And he instructed the leaders of the city not to enforce the law, not to enforce immigration law.\"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_628", "prompt": "Says Americans invented Pong, Space Invaders and the iPhone.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_629", "prompt": "Says Oregons high minimum wage is the reason why by 2011, Oregons restaurants employed an average of only 13.8 workers, or 2.6 fewer employees than they did before the states minimum wage began rising above the federal level in 1997.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_630", "prompt": "In 40 years, 23,000 chemicals came on the market and only four were regulated.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_631", "prompt": "Rubio's \"got more experience than Obama had.\"", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_632", "prompt": "Im the only candidate for governor whos rolled out any policies so far.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_633", "prompt": "On military recruiters at Harvard, Elena Kagan \"took a position and the Supreme Court ruled unanimously that she was wrong.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_634", "prompt": "SaysCongressman Jack Kingston voted to raise his pay seven times.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_635", "prompt": "Says Obamacare is the largest middle-class tax increase in history.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_636", "prompt": "Says the United States is in the worst recovery from an economic recession since World War II.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_637", "prompt": "Says the Clintons burst through their own self-pronounced guidelines by acceptingforeign donations.There is a clip of Bill Clinton saying were not going to take foreign donations.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_638", "prompt": "Cap-and-trade is wildly unpopular with Americans.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_639", "prompt": "ISIS is in 32 countries.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_640", "prompt": "In 1992, Barack Obama directed \"Project Vote - an arm of ACORN that also encouraged voter registration.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_641", "prompt": "Says Panasonic stayed in New Jersey because of the Business Retention and Relocation Assistance Grant (BRRAG) program.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_642", "prompt": "Rick Scott has paid down our debt by about $2 billion. Charlie Crists debt went up about $5 billion.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_643", "prompt": "I helped write the Affordable Care Act.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_644", "prompt": "Right now were the highest taxed country in the world.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_645", "prompt": "President Obama and Democrats spending addiction has driven our national debt to historic proportions, maxed out our national credit card and has now led to the Democrat Downgrade of our countrys AAA credit rating.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_646", "prompt": "Live cats have holes drilled into their skulls, posts put into their heads and coils put into their eyes, and some have had their ears cut off or are intentionally deafened or starved at UW-Madison labs that do research to improve hearing in humans.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_647", "prompt": "Republicans are trying to impeach our president.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_648", "prompt": "Says President Barack Obama is responsible for pending defense cuts.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_649", "prompt": "There are already more American jobs in the solar industry than in coal mining.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_650", "prompt": "Says Florida U.S. Reps. Corrine Brown, Alcee Hastings and Frederica Wilson are Socialists.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_651", "prompt": "The United States has never been richer, if you look at per capita GDP.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_652", "prompt": "Boeing is building a brand new 747 Air Force One for future presidents, but costs are out of control, more than $4 billion. Cancel order!", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_653", "prompt": "Mequon and Milwaukee have the highest disparity of income in the country.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_654", "prompt": "Before the HOPE scholarship, 70 percent of the high school students who made 1400 or above on their SAT left the state of Georgia. Now, 70 percent of those stay in the state of Georgia.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_655", "prompt": "Four out of 10 homicides are committed by gun in this city.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_656", "prompt": "The richest 1 percent of America will get a bigger tax cut through this bill than the family income of the average family here in Central Texas.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_657", "prompt": "Abortion is the second-most conducted surgical procedure in this country.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_658", "prompt": "\"I didn't endorse\" the federal stimulus bill.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_659", "prompt": "Our president has labeled Americans as soft.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_660", "prompt": "Says John Boehner admits we are not going to be any different than weve been by returning to the same failed economic policies that wrecked our economy.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_661", "prompt": "By releasing only basic tax information, former U.S. Congressman Nathan Deal is hiding more than hes disclosed about his business dealing with the state.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_662", "prompt": "Illegal immigration costs state taxpayers over $3 billion every year.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_663", "prompt": "You would receive a citation for taking a dildo to class at the University of Texas.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_664", "prompt": "Says Allen West helped thwart a terrorist plot by shooting a gun in the direction of an Iraqi detainee, then reported the incident to his superior and said it was wrong.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_665", "prompt": "Its taken more time to complete the Towpath Trail than it did to build the (Ohio Erie) Canal.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_666", "prompt": "Says sixty-two percent of small businesses over the last five years went under because they couldnt pay their health care bills.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_667", "prompt": "State school funding per pupil is down 16 percent compared to 2009, after adjusting for inflation.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_668", "prompt": "Before 2005, the percentage of Texas high school students meeting the college readiness standards of the Texas Higher Education Coordinating Board stood at 28% in English and 42% in math. Those figures stood at 65% and 66% in 2013.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_669", "prompt": "Says Mitt Romneys carried interest income was a tax trick.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_670", "prompt": "Palin \"fired Wasilla's Police Chief because he 'intimidated' her.\"", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_671", "prompt": "You go down to Miami and when its flooding at high tide on a sunny day, fish are swimming through the middle of the streets.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_672", "prompt": "\"Congress' approval rating is 11 percent. You know who's higher? Dick Cheney and HMOs.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_673", "prompt": "In the past two years in Congress, Ive written more bills, passed more amendments on the floor of the House and enacted more of my bills into law than any other member of the House.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_674", "prompt": "On the use of presidentially appointed commissions.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_675", "prompt": "Obama \"shunned the opportunity to talk to soldiers to thank them for their service.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_676", "prompt": "Supreme Court nominee Merrick Garland voted to uphold D.C.s ban on handguns.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_677", "prompt": "The ACLU has filed a suit to end prayer from the military completely.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_678", "prompt": "\"(My dad) used to campaign against the gas-guzzling dinosaurs.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_679", "prompt": "Says Gov. Scott Walker is cooking the books by releasing numbers he just dreamed up that show Wisconsin gained jobs in 2011.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_680", "prompt": "When Republican extremists tried to take away abortion rights Blake Rocap stopped them.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_681", "prompt": "Sarah Palin \"has had 12 years of elected office experience.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_682", "prompt": "Barbara Boxer voted to cut spending on Medicare benefits by $500 billion, cuts so costly to hospitals and nursing homes that they could stop taking Medicare altogether.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_683", "prompt": "Were taxing our small businesses now at rates higher than corporations.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_684", "prompt": "In Afghanistan \"the (military) leadership has proposed a new medal, an award for 'Courageous Restraint' ... for 'NOT FIRING BACK.' \"", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_685", "prompt": "Says we are going to sell this house and use the proceeds to stabilize rates.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_686", "prompt": "Says the United States has treaties with apparently 69 countries where we are obligated to defend their borders. And these were treaties that were executive treaties, not authorized by Congress.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_687", "prompt": "Says Julie Parrish wants to add a sales tax to everything we need to buy including food, clothing, medicine and school supplies.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_688", "prompt": "Between 2000 and 2010, the illegal immigrant population of Texas increased by 60 percent, while California and Florida had no increase.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_689", "prompt": "Says she made an accurate prediction that if Barack Obama were elected it would encourage Russia to invade Ukraine.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_690", "prompt": "Says the media distortedwhat happened with a baby at his rally.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_691", "prompt": "Says Patrick Murphy never worked as a CPA and was never a small business owner.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_692", "prompt": "Says the majority of Americans support gay marriage.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_693", "prompt": "When Mitt Romney was governor, Massachusetts ranked 47th out of 50 states in job creation.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_694", "prompt": "If you look at the income of average Americans...theyre absolutely flat in constant dollars since 1979.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_695", "prompt": "For the first time since the Korean War, total federal spending has gone down for two years in a row.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_696", "prompt": "Under President Bush in eight years, we added $4.9 trillion to the debt. Under President Obama, weve added $5.3 trillion to the debt in the 3.5 years hes been in office.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_697", "prompt": "Under the new health care law, the first person (a) patient has to go to is a bureaucrat. That is called a panel.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_698", "prompt": "Both McCain and Bush favor tax breaks for oil companies.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_699", "prompt": "By 2014, there will be one administrator for every teacher on college campuses in the United States.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_700", "prompt": "And, as of today, New Jersey state government has less employees than when Christie Whitman left office in 2001.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_701", "prompt": "Says the State Department spent $630,000 to get 2 million Facebook Likes.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_702", "prompt": "Two years ago motorists in Ferguson, a city of 20,000 people, received 31,000 citations. Thats at least one citation per person plus 10,000 for visitors. The city is still surviving only on traffic tickets; theres virtually no industry there.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_703", "prompt": "Bill McCollum \"served as a lobbyist whose clients enabled mortgages for illegal immigrants.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_704", "prompt": "Obamacarerepresents the largest tax increase in the history of the world.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_705", "prompt": "Right now, America has $1.1 trillion of student debt. Thats more than credit card debt.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_706", "prompt": "Says U.S. Senate rival Tommy Thompson ran Medicare into the ground and nine years closer to bankruptcy.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_707", "prompt": "Rhode Island: 3% bigger at low tide.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_708", "prompt": "Says President Barack Obama has an Environmental Protection Agency proposal that would raise the price of gasoline by 25 cents a gallon.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_709", "prompt": "In Virginias Medicaid program, approximately 30 percent, or $2.7 billion a year, is lost to waste, fraud and inefficiencies.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_710", "prompt": "In the past 20 years, Egypt has made great strides in political and democratic reform.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_711", "prompt": "Says, In the last four years weve cut $36 million in ongoing revenue.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_712", "prompt": "Republican leadership took the lead confirming Loretta Lynch as attorney general.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_713", "prompt": "In terms of the wealthiest Americans, were at the lowest tax rate since the 1950s.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_714", "prompt": "Were making more than ever off oil and gas right now, but its no secret that oil production in Texas peaked in the 1970s.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_715", "prompt": "Says Hillary Clinton wants sanctuary cities.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_716", "prompt": "I have won more elections than any chairman since 1938.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_717", "prompt": "Since the beginning of the year weve created a net increase of 45,000 jobs.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_718", "prompt": "Says Ron Johnson referred to The Lego Movie as an insidious anti-business conspiracy.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_719", "prompt": "When you look at the number of crashes before the cameras were installed compared to after, theyre virtually the same.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_720", "prompt": "\"The estate tax, which came into being by Republicans like Teddy Roosevelt and others ... is there for a real simple reason: In America, we've never liked the idea of massive inherited wealth.\"", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_721", "prompt": "While Mandels been busy traveling the country raising campaign money, he hasnt shown up for work.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_722", "prompt": "When George W. Bush was governor of Texas, the percentage uninsured went down. Under his successor, Rick Perry, its gone up.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_723", "prompt": "More 25- to 34-year-olds are moving to Austin than any other city in America.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_724", "prompt": "Protesters in La Crosse blocked an exit and surrounded a State Patrol car carrying the governor and were beating on the windows and rocking the vehicle. When the car was extricated from the crowd, a truck blocked a second exit.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_725", "prompt": "Says Barack Obama was silent on Iran when the students took to the streets in Tehran and the people there protested, (and) the Green Revolution occurred.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_726", "prompt": "The General Assembly has no explicit constitutional authority to impose income, sales, estate and the myriad of other taxes upon us.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_727", "prompt": "Says the New York Times can write a story that they know is false yet they cant basically be sued.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_728", "prompt": "Says Paul Ryan shut off the C-SPAN cameras when the Democrats started their sit-in.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_729", "prompt": "Because of (U.S. Sen.-elect Ron) Johnsons leadership, Senate Republicans adopted a caucus ban on earmarks.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_730", "prompt": "Says Obamaexempted Congress and their staff from the full effect of the (health care) law.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_731", "prompt": "The average age of first marijuana use is 12.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_732", "prompt": "Just about everyone everywhere is spending more hours on the job, less time with their families, bringing home smaller and smaller paychecks, while theyre paying more and more at the gas pump and the grocery stores.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_733", "prompt": "Half of all NC legislative candidates are unopposed because of gerrymandering.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_734", "prompt": "One-half of undocumented workers pay federal income taxes, which means they are paying more federal income taxes than Donald Trump pays.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_735", "prompt": "In 2007, when Nancy Pelosi met with President Assad of Syria, nobody got upset.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_736", "prompt": "A space shuttle the National Museum of the United States Air Force near Dayton would be within a days drive of 60 percent of the U.S. population.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_737", "prompt": "Says Milwaukee County spent over $170,000 in salaries in 2010 for employees to participate in union activities such as collective bargaining.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_738", "prompt": "Its estimated that 40 percent of all the guns that are sold in the United States occur with no background records check.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_739", "prompt": "Says there are fewer jobs in America today than when Barack Obama became president.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_740", "prompt": "Georgia is one of only about seven states in the country that has a AAA bond rating.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_741", "prompt": "[W]hen adjusted for cost of living, Georgia ranks first nationally in teacher salary and benefits.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_742", "prompt": "Says PolitiFact has said he kept a campaign promise to toughen ethics rules.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_743", "prompt": "The passage of the teacher tenure bill in the Fla. Legislature was like the health care bill in Congress because one party jammed it through.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_744", "prompt": "On hearings about automatic citizenship provision in U.S. Constitution.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_745", "prompt": "Texas Governor Rick Perrys voter ID law is a blatant effort to defeat Wendy Davis by disenfranchising tens of thousands of women voters.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_746", "prompt": "Says the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act adopted last year contains a series of slush funds, set up to stay on the books automatically, with little or no oversight.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_747", "prompt": "A 2005 gay pride vote had nothing to do with discrimination.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_748", "prompt": "The state of Georgia is near the bottom among states for SAT scores and graduation rates.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_749", "prompt": "Today 46 percent of all Floridians owe more on their home than it is worth.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_750", "prompt": "Saturdays shootings reflect a disturbing trend. Mass shootings have become commonplace since the Virginia Tech massacre in 2007. There have been dozens of incidents where three or more people have been fatally wounded. Hundreds have died.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_751", "prompt": "Says a gun bill before the Senate would make it a federal felony to leave town for more than seven days, and leave someone else at home with your firearms.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_752", "prompt": "Between 2010 and 2014, there was no net in-migration from Mexico.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_753", "prompt": "Obama thinks the national anthem should be \"I'd Like to Teach the World to Sing.\"", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_754", "prompt": "John McCain opposed bankruptcy protections for families \"who were only in bankruptcy because of medical expenses they couldn't pay.\"", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_755", "prompt": "The Republican candidate [John Loughlin] has talked about privatizing Social Security ... so we know where he stands on the issue.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_756", "prompt": "Ohioans want an end to pay-to-play politics.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_757", "prompt": "Our children do not spend any time in school learning about our own U.S. Constitution.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_758", "prompt": "When total Sandy spending is added up, its more than the annual budget for the U.S. Department of Homeland Security. And its more than twice the annual budget of the U.S. Energy Department.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_759", "prompt": "\ufeffSays JoAnne Kloppenburgs side had a 3-to-1 money advantage in the Wisconsin Supreme Court campaign.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_760", "prompt": "Says Thomas Jefferson said, You might be able to fool the people for awhile, and they may go astray, but sooner or later the American people are going to wake up and they will correct the course.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_761", "prompt": "Before this day is out, 18 more veterans will have taken their own lives. That is the daily average, it is intolerable, and it has to stop.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_762", "prompt": "Says Rick Perrys proposal on driver licenses and high school dropouts has been state law since 1989.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_763", "prompt": "Now we have ISIS coming over the (U.S.-Mexico) border.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_764", "prompt": "Boston Marathon bombing suspect Tamerlan Tsarnaev is buried not far from President Kennedys grave.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_765", "prompt": "Georgia has one of the nations highest jet fuel taxes.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_766", "prompt": "In Africa, a child dies every minute because of (malaria).", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_767", "prompt": "\"There's no rationing in any of these bills.\"", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_768", "prompt": "Allowing all Bush income tax cuts to expire on Dec. 31 will amount to the largest tax increase in the history of America.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_769", "prompt": "Says Barack Obama was happily photographed holding a T-shirt with revolutionary Ernesto Che Guevaras face on it.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_770", "prompt": "In 2008, then-Sen. Barack Obama missed 60 or 70 percent of his votes. In 2004, John Kerry missed close to 60 to 70 percent and Bob Graham missed over 30 percent of his votes.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_771", "prompt": "Says Paul Ryan tried to change the whole game for Social Security", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_772", "prompt": "Says as Indiana governor, he has made record investments in education.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_773", "prompt": "The so-called defense minister of the Peoples Republic of Donetsk ... actually posted a bragging social media posting of having shot down a military transport. And then when it became apparent it was civilian, they pulled it down from social media.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_774", "prompt": "Says his Texas election fraud investigations have resulted in 50 convictions.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_775", "prompt": "The Benghazi victims were left helpless to die as Hillary Clinton soundly slept in her bed.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_776", "prompt": "Says Donald Trumps Make America Great Again caps are made in China.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_777", "prompt": "A recent economic uptick appears to coincide with the expectation of a new Republican Congress.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_778", "prompt": "Private prisons do not chase escaped inmates past the perimeter like the public prisons do, which means more escaped prisoners in our communities.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_779", "prompt": "Warren Buffett called (Jeff) Greenes scheme financial weapons of mass destruction.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_780", "prompt": "Politician Reid Ribble wants to phase out Social Security, forcing Wisconsin seniors to fend for themselves.", "answer": 5, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_781", "prompt": "Floridas revenue is growing at a faster rate than almost any state in the country.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_782", "prompt": "Women still do not get paid as much as men, even for the same work, period.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_783", "prompt": "Says that since 1975, redistricting by Texas lawmakers has always been found in violation of Section 5 of the Voting Rights Act.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_784", "prompt": "Theres been no conclusive or specific report to say Russia was trying to muddy the election.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_785", "prompt": "Says if you try to hide marijuana in a hemp field, it becomes worthless. The THC goes away.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_786", "prompt": "Says Travis County Commissioner Gerald Daugherty claims to have taken a pay cut, but for 2016, he voted to raise his salary by 19.6 percent.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_787", "prompt": "We continue to see these isolated incidents of people trying to vote five, six times a day.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_788", "prompt": "Says that 9 million to 50 million undocumented immigrants live in the United States.", "answer": 4, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_789", "prompt": "Ive been involved in prosecuting a terrorist member of ISIS.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_790", "prompt": "Romneycare sent costs spiraling out of control in Massachusetts, hiking premiums, squeezing household budgets.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_791", "prompt": "$6 billion water bond program voters passed in 2011 has yet to be tapped.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_792", "prompt": "Says the Obama administration never responded to his 2012 letter flagging the uptick in unaccompanied children crossing the U.S.-Mexico border.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_793", "prompt": "Undocumented immigrantspay $12 billion a year into Social Security.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_794", "prompt": "Mitt Romney gave away his fathers inheritance.", "answer": 3, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_795", "prompt": "Says President Obama helped more than half a million veterans and military family members go to college through the Post-9/11 G.I. Bill.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_796", "prompt": "Obama says hes put forward a specific $4 trillion deficit reduction plan.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_797", "prompt": "Says the main Central Texas food bank is delivering 50 percent more food to the poor than three years ago.", "answer": 2, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_798", "prompt": "Says Congressman Bill Pascrell voted to remove the public option from the Affordable Health Care Act.", "answer": 0, "domain": "fact_verification"}, {"id": "liar_799", "prompt": "It costs a hell of a lot more money to put somebody in jail than send them to the University of Virginia.", "answer": 1, "domain": "fact_verification"}]